okay today is video 30 and I couldn't do
100 like I've said in the last few
videos I don't know if I'm to make all
hundred cuz I'm not getting the same I'm
not getting anything like I'm not sound
I'm not getting anything either but it's
just to check it's not actually
motivating me to learn how to edit so
cuz I do one a day overwhelming but
that's how I originally started was to
explain Michael cooperative and so I'm
gonna take the opportunity to do that
today as many days as I need to with - I
have to do hundred of those I think that
was originally the point of these and
then I was watching Kanye's videos and I
wanted to start being more vulnerable
and explaining more of myself which I'll
still do I'm just gonna figure out what
days I feel like doing what and where I
don't know what to talk about I don't
have a topic to talk about I will talk
about the global cooperative and
discussing this morning with my roommate
what what those things look like and I
love having discussion that should be
the video I do like stuff that I need
the other person to be okay with being
on video but just recording discussions
of the global cooperative and people
bringing up issues like what what about
this like I just feel like it's the
answer to everything I was saying that I
don't know what the next step is I know
what all that and I do I do know what it
is I have it it's done I mean it's not
done you actually do it
the preliminary idea and it isn't for me
to be the leader and or the person with
all the solutions it's to create a
system that enables us to easily
implement solutions from the discussing
the problem that the solution solves or
makes better - even if you come with
that idea already there implementing it
like how do you actually get it to the
people who need it without taking a lot
of risk it without spending a lot of
money without anything coming from it
and we need solutions on this planet
like that's what we are desperately in
need of is solutions for everything for
education system for our healthcare
systems for our transportation system
for racism and sexist
which need solutions all kinds of them
and the system right now is designed
that it has to be marketable and even if
that means you're in here an NGO
starting nonprofit and you still be
marketable yourself have enough of a
market if people give you money I'm just
really passionate about sharing
knowledge and connection so that's like
communities relationships and I've been
searching for the former my whole well
most of my life this idea of this like
group that accepts me as the individual
that I am and also I'm able to
contribute to and just feel fulfilled
being part of it's something that the
constant theme I've been seeking and as
for all of the themes in my life
realizing I'm actually exactly where I'm
supposed to be and surrounded by amazing
people even if it doesn't look like what
I thought it would look like where it's
like you know I don't know grew up in
the friends era of like six friends you
get together and have coffee every day
and Co over to each other's house it is
and we're like a unit and that's never
been my life so why I thought that was
gonna just materialize it nowhere but
that's part of it's not talking with a
little paw burger today at least I'm not
like pitchy and the whole thing but some
of us suck at finding relationships
whether they're the entire community or
significant other friendships and I
think technology can help us with that
it already has with online dating but
then we have issues with online dating
and online dating is designed to be it
was designed for extroverts designed for
people who may come off good in pictures
or in writing and can solve themselves
and but does it necessarily those are
the people who are the best at
relationships and then there's people
who aren't good at relationships
themselves and being able to have a
system that walks you through how to
deal with an issue in your relationship
or how to come to a decision together
how to make up after a fight how to keep
the spark alive in a relationship I
think technology talked with all about
it does mean it's only technology of
course this tool behind it but
I mean I know I'm pretty good at
maintaining a relationship it's the
getting into relationship but maybe not
so great at and I know for if I'm with a
good human being I always am because I
mean you're not gonna last a baby we're
not a good human being that
concentrating on the good is what keeps
it good because everyone has good and
bad about them if you concentrate on the
negative which is what it's naturally
for us to do we get together with
friends we bitch about our significant
others when we get together online it's
like we bitch about our jobs but that
then that's what we focus on we focus on
the net so then we're concepts like they
chew it they're both open and that's
like oh we can hear it it just grows and
it becomes bigger in our relationship as
opposed to taking time to without the
other person even present realizing what
we're grateful for with them right and I
do with my own life we've been if not
with relationships and some not in one
but like when I find myself annoyed at a
human being that I do love did you just
sit and be like what but what do I love
about them and it can be a hard a hard
thing to do in that moment but it's it's
well worth it and we're in a
relationship it's even more important to
take that time to be grateful for who
they are and what they do for themselves
for the world for you and concentrate on
the positive and I think we can create
apps like on earth do that taps that
help with co-parenting when you're maybe
not getting along with your ex apps that
help you we just there's so many ways to
connect with community and be able to
find your spot that you fit in because
the chance that you're born and raised
and get to be your own unique self
within this within the culture and group
that you were born and raised in to its
near impossible the chance that you like
that's your essential self is that your
ax wasp right what is that white
anglo-saxon Protestant but that's your
house Colleen it's like the chance if
you're born into your eyes calling hope
you're not so great so you have to
overcome things to get there but
whatever
today is day 30 I'm still here I'm still
figuring out how to
operative as well as how to be more
authentically me so loving my haircut
even though it's clear that I'm gonna
need hair care products okay I think the
do its own thing another good slog it up
it's gonna be I'll be eating a little
bit place right it's a holiday I didn't
post yesterday cuz my child was home
sick but I'm making it today so today is
day 30 and I will see you on my name